Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed during the
filming of this series.
You'll stop, Nayman.
- You and your soldiers will stop.
- Who will make me?
Cengiz Khan's seal.
Soldiers!
Attack!
It's commander Nayman's order!
I'm the real owner of the seal.
You... You did this Osman.
You were gaining time.
You were the one who
wanted to gain time.
I came face to face with you.
You were the one who
put forward the Alps.
What's wrong? Your
plan didn't work?
Is that why you are barking like a dog?
I swear to Sky Tengri, I'll kill you!
I will!
Marmaracık Castle
Aktemur.
When my mother finds out about the plan
you played with Osman Bey, it won't be good.
Alçiçek.
You know that I had to do it.
Bengi Mother will understand me.
Thank Allah.
Mashallah to my children!
You took back what my Öktem
entrusted to us. Thank Allah.
We did , mother. We took
revenge of our soldiers.
I knew you wouldn't
fail me, son.
Thanks mother.
We took the castle.
It will be Nayman's turn now.
Inshallah.
My daughter!
On the way, the Alps talked
about your skills. Mashallah.
Who helped you from inside?
Mother, who is going to help us?
There's no such thing.
Alps and Alçiçek entered
through the secret passage.
They were probably
talking about that.
Good.
Send the news!
Say that, Aktemur, the Bey of Kargın Tribe,
made Marmaracık a Turkish homeland again!
Let's go.
We have many things to do.
Aktemur Bey, let's clean our lands...
which were polluted by infidels.
Drop your sword and
surrender, Nayman!
Never!
Catch him.
Stop Shaman, too!
I won't die today
to kill you, Osman!
I will come to kill you!
Your end has come.
You cannot kill me.
You won't even be able to build a state.
Come on.
- Osman!
- Take him.
- So you are Osman Bey.
- So, you are Gazan Khan's commander.
Bagatur.
Commander Bagatur.
I understand.
- Welcome, Commander.
- Thank you, Osman Bey.
We received the letter you
made Sultan Alaaddin send to us.
When we found Talay, Turgut
Bey had already killed him.
And we came to your
land with Turgut Bey.
We captured this traitor.
Commander.
This traitor will
never be free!
You can be sure.
I didn't come here to free the traitor.
He has no power now.
But my Alps have to come with you...
...for me to not worry.
Don't you trust us, Osman Bey?
I do but precaution does not harm us.
Soldiers!
We are going back!
Alps will accompany us.
- May you go safely.
- Thank you.
Alps!
You will accompany the Commander.
Come on!
Alps!
Have a good rest.
We'll keep conquering lands.
The war has just started for us!
Yes, my Bey.
We're going to Turgut Bey.
Come on.
Where are they taking
Nayman, Mother Sultan?
Osman is playing a game, Celali.
But we will find out what it is.
- Any news from Karavul?
- He knows we'll meet here.
Good.
Karavul..
You will go after Nayman.
You will walk in
the dark.
You will learn where they are going
and what they are up to.
Your command, the owner
of the Seljuk state.
Osman left the field
with a victory today.
His control over the borders will be
stronger. Beys will gather behind him.
But I will prevent this from happening.
Come on.
My Bey... I put acacia herb in it.
It will heal your eyes.
O healer.
Thank you.
Thank you, Kumral Abdal. Thank you.
Turgut Bey is coming
Osman Bey...
My Osman Bey..
- Are you okay?
- I am okay.
I am fine, don't worry.
Thank you. You've done
a very tough duty.
We handled it with our minds, what
we couldn't handle with our hands.
Yes! Good!
- Are you alright?
- I am, I am, don't worry.
Thanks to Kumral Abdal.
My Bey, we were waiting for your
order with our bows.
However, Nayman wasn't granted with the
rope of the bow, but the hangman's knot!
Gazan Khan will deal with
the Nayman issue now.
Now... they will be after them as a
precaution until they leave our lands.
Now, Nayman is not our issue.
Our issue is conquest, as always.
It is conquest!
Alps! We will never stop.
We will keep going.
Now... All of you will
gather information for me.
And we will detect the places
that are closest to the conquest.
Cerkutay.
- My Bey.
- Geyve area is yours.
Spy that place and bring me all the
information.
Yes my Bey.
- Aykurt.
- My Bey.
- You will deal with Akhisar.
- Yes my Bey.
Şamil! You will go to Tekirpınar Castle.
Yes, my Bey.
- Baysungur.
- I'm listening my Bey.
- You'll deal with Güblüce.
- Yes, my Bey.
- Gürbüz.
- My Bey.
- You will deal with Kızılhisar.
- Yes, my Bey.
Konur.
You will go to Köprühisar.
I want to be informed about the condition
of the citadel in detail.
Yes, my Bey.
- Turgut.
- Tell me.
I will not let you rest.
Only our death can stop us.
You'll prepare conquest
equipments for us.
- Your command.
- Thank you.
- Turahan.
- My Bey.
Go to the tribe of Bayram Bey, who was
martyred. Meet all their needs.
Yes, my Bey.
Alps. I want to have all the
information until iftar.
Intelligence is the key to victory.
Come on, Alps.
- Yes, my Bey
- My Bey.
- My children.
Come here.
Bagatur!
Cengiz's seal is mine!
You took my seal!
And I will kill you!
With which power, Nayman?
Do you trust a few marauders
from your army?
A brave person is better
than a thousand cowards.
I'll be enough for all of you!
All of you!
You only gnaw the state...
that Cengiz Khan established.
But you will be punished accordingly.
You will not be saved from
Gazan Khan's wrath.
No one against Sky
Tengri will hurt great Nayman.
You are responsible
for all of this, Shaman.
We will soon arrive Tebriz.
Let us get there,
then you will be punished as well!
Brothers.
We'll part ways soon.
Let me give you some clues.
- What clue is that?
- You know,
what is spying and how to spy.
For example...
this road leads to Geyve.
Look how I found my way!
We know as much as you do.
As much as me?
For example, what would you do if
you were about to be exposed in an infidel city?
How can you escape?
How can you disguise?
Do you know that?
I know. I was with infidels
for years...
and I didn't expose anything.
Cerkutay, why are you boasting?
For example, Konur brother
is also very competent at spying.
Thank you.
When I was in Köprühisar, I got
over many troubles,
but I didn't give up. Why?
Because Cerkutay does not give up.
Oh, İnegöl. I disguised many
times before Olof's eyes...
and nobody realized.
You have a lot to learn from Cerkutay.
Oh, Cerkutay.
They won't understand, anyway.
Let's go.
Still no news.
- It's so hard to wait.
- Are you worried about Cerkutay Alp?
Don't be.
Don't be afraid. He has double
swords, so he will be alright.
Inshallah.
Who are you waiting for, girl?
Cerku... Mother!
I'm not waiting for anyone.
Alps... Yes.
They're in a battle.
If you're waiting for nobody,
why are you watching the gate?
I was just looking...
Because of the battle, you know.
- Do you have someone in your heart?
- No. It's empty.
My heart is empty.
Are you sure?
Mother.
Mother! They're here!
They're here.
Welcome. Welcome.
You saved me!
Ülgen, any news from Osman Bey?
No.
We were waiting too.
What about you?
Did you take the citadel?
Yes, we did.
Did you have doubts?
No.
Mashallah, hatuns.
If I wasn't old, I'd go with you
and behead the infidels!
You're not that old, midwife.
Mashallah, you can still draw swords.
I've brought news from Osman Bey.
Are they okay?
What about the battle?
They're all good.
The result is victory.
He invited Beys for an iftar dinner
and he told me to let you know.
Thank Allah.
Yes, thank Allah.
For iftar?
Today?
Beys? A feast?
Oh Allah!
How can we cook so much food?
Run, Esma!
- Run, Esma.
- Come on!
Sons.
You must be wondering why we are here.
Look arond.
We're at Avdan Mountain.
If you go that way, you
will end up in Köprühisar.
If you go that way,
...then infidels will be
waiting for you in Kızılhisar.
All around the mountain...
there are citadels and castles that our
Alps have gone to discover.
You say there are many
obstacles in our route, my Bey.
Not obstacles, my Bey says we have
much work and many conquests ahead.
When the citadels mentioned are defeated,
two ways leading to İznik will be opened.
You say nobody can stop us from capturing
İznik and the towns around, brother.
Sons, I say just one...
...but you hear a thousand.
Mashallah!
Our destination and target are certain.
When ALps bring information,
we'll choose a way.
- Your command, my Bey.
Thank you, my brave sons.
Let's go!
Soldiers, leave him and get out.
I got your note, Bayindir.
Mashallah.
You explained everything in detail...
Bayındır.
How you served Nayman like a dog.
How you sold me out.
How you got defeated by Turgut.
Sun of Seljuks, Mighty Mother
Sultan, please forgive me!
I messed everything up!
That's why I wrote what
I did in the note.
In case you spare my life.
Great Mother Sultan, forgive me.
Well thought, Bayındır.
Very well thought!
If you hadn't sent me this note,
you'd be dead as soon as you enter Söğüt.
But I won't forgive you anyway, Bayındır.
You cut off my head, Mighty Mother Sultan.
Instead of Osman or the
dog called Nayman,
I'd prefer Mother Sultan, the undying
sun of Seljuks to cut... --
Shut up!
Stop trembling before me!
You've lived dishonorably.
Die honorably, at least.
Haven't you disgraced yourself enough?
Mighty Mother Sultan, I
swear on Allah and everything.
I want to live just to undo
my disgraceful actions!
I'm begging for one last chance.
One last chance.
So be it.
You'll clean all the dirty things
you've done, Bayındır.
You'll die if I tell you to die.
You'll kill if I tell you to kill.
Your command, Mother Sultan!
I'll sacrifice my life for you if
necessary, Mighty Mother Sultan.
Whatever you wish!
However,
that dog called Nayman will kill me
when he sees me.
What about that?
Don't worry about Nayman.
Osman arrested him.
Now go and wait for my call.
Your command.
Prepare my horse, Celali.
Bayındır.
How can I cook so much in time?
Come on, Esma.
You've done nothing yet?
Esma, get to the dough.
The dark Midwife.
Let me do it, Ülgen.
Come on.
What are you doing?
What does it look like, Ülgen?
I mean... I see, but..
Come on, Ülgen. Stop looking.
Chop the onions.
- I got the bread.
- Good.
Move aside, girl.
Esma.
Are you single?
Do you have anyone in your heart?
Ülgen's heart is empty.
Is yours empty too?
I'll make Ülgen get married first.
Then, you will be the next.
We won't miss Selcan Hatun thanks to
you, right, the dark midwife?
She was just like you.
She'd make us prepare the wedding
ceremony when she saw someone single.
Selcan Hatun...
May Allah let her be in heaven.
- Amin.
But Hatuns, you have never worked.
Yenişehir is full of single people.
But I'll take make them get married.
You are right, the dark midwife.
Hatuns, we have to do
something about this.
Mother! Enough.
You're always talking about marriage!
I am, why do you care?
You talk too much!
You have to marry!
Hatuns!
Do you know any brave single man?
Actually there is someone.
- Don't say it!
- He is...
He is very talented.
He even use double swords!
Mashallah.
Double swords?
Did I see him? Who is that?
You saw him, the dark midwife.
Don't...
One of Osman Bey's Alps...
Cerkutay...
You are talking about that crazy man?
Is he single?
But no. I won't give my daughter
to someone who is crazy.
I'm unfortunate!
I was just about to say
everything is alright.
Now, this happens!
My Allah, give me patience.
Cerkutay, look what you did!
Ülgen.
- Ülgen!
- What?
Why are you crying?
No.
I'm not crying.
Osman Bey is coming!
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Since you are all here,
it means that missions are completed.
May you all live long.
Now, tell me which fortresses
and castles are wating...
for us to conquest?
- Aykurt.
- My Bey.
Akhisar.
Protected by crossbowmen.
Every corner? Isn't there a way?
No, my Bey. They
are protecting every inch of the castle.
- Anything else?
- The conquest might e hard.
And it's far away from here.
During the siege, our back
will be vulnerable, my Bey.
- This area?
- Yes, my Bey.
Thank you.
- Şamil?
- My Bey.
Tekirpınar Castle is in
the same situation.
Tell me.
Also the soldiers are well trained.
Anything else?
- That's all, my Bey.
- Alright.
My Bey.
To conquer
the castles in question, first of all...
we need to take Geyve Citadel. (castle)
First Geyve, is that so?
Tell me about it.
This is the key my Bey. If
we take it, the rest will come.
But,
the state is the same in here as well.
- The ones that lead...
- What do they say?
They scare people and say
that Turks are cruel.
Okay.
- Baysungur.
- My Bey.
It's the same in Lüblüce, my Bey.
They keep saying Turks are cruel.
Gürbüz, it's the same
there too, I guess.
My Bey.
It's the same in Kızılhisar as well.
Okay.
What about Konur?
Konur is the only one remaining
who did not bring news.
- Boran?
- My Bey.
- Hasn't he arrived yet?
- He'll be here soon, my Bey.
Okay.
We will determine our route based on
the information we will have from Konur.
- Have Konur visit me when he arrives.
- Yes, my Bey.
We will end our fasting in the
caravanserai in Karakuyu.
We will spend the night there.
Take precautions.
Your fast will be broken with
your own blood.
Don't worry, Nayman.
As long as I have the seal, no power
can prevent us from going Tebriz.
You will not be able to save
your head, Nayman.
Tell me.
- Why were you late?
- They know, my Bey.
They know that they have the secret.
They took precautions.
What is the condition of Köprühisar?
Köprühisar is the toughest
place among these, my Bey.
They know that we will come.
They raised the walls.
Workers are doing their
best.
They even removed the hidden
passages Gürbüz talked about.
Detecting the new ones
will take quite a time.
Even those passages are defended...
by soldiers with human-sized
shields who came from Byzantium.
We can deal with the shields.
Everything is clear now.
We will go to Köprühisar.
The toughest one is Köprühisar
among these places my Bey.
How do we get through the shields when
it's impossible find the passages?
I would like to know why.
First,
Köprühisar will open...
the gate of whole conquest, the gates
of Bursa and İznik.
Second, Köprühisar's key...
is with us.
What kind of key is this, my Bey?
Every thing has a master.
You will take this to the
person who built those passages.
Give this to him. And he will give
you the map of passages.
Who does that master serve, my Bey?
Who is he?
- Can we trust him?
- Yes.
We do.
Don't worry. The ink is the
proof of everything.
And he promised a favor to us.
But... without the ink,
there will be no map.
Without the map, there
won't be a conquest.
You will bring the map to me until
the sunset tomorrow. Tell the Alps.
- They should be ready for the war.
- Yes my Bey.
You are thinking about
why we trust him,huh?
Yes, my Bey.
I took it from the
ones I consult...
...when walking on our way.
Now.. Tell the Alps.
They should take those shields.
Yes, my Bey. If you allow me.
Sure, you can go.
Mashallah.
You did everything you said.
You made Aktemur the Bey.
You took Marmaracık.
You don't ever let me down, Bengi.
Yes, Mother Sultan.
I was not expecting this.
He turned out to be braver than I thought.
Mashallah.
Is he still not talking to his uncle Osman?
He is not. There is no relation
left between him and Osman.
If Osman is not behind him, I am behind him.
The one who stands under the
shadow doesn't have a shadow.
Aktemur did the right thing.
We definitely need a bigger victory for
Aktemur to gain people's trust.
We need more power for
big victories.
We need your power Mother Sultan.
- Mother Sultan.
- Tell me, Celali.
Osman Bey sent news. He is inviting
you to iftar in his mansion.
He also invited the Beys.
Since he has gotten rid of Nayman...
he is trying to show off now.
He is still breathing.
This is not justice.
That is Osman's justice, Bengi Hatun.
Celali. Prepare good gifts for Beys.
We must remind them that
we have the power...
and their leashes.
My Sultan, you brought pleasure.
I found pleasure here, Aktemur Bey.
Come on, get ready.
You will also come to Yenişehir.
- My Sultan, my uncle and I...
- I know.
You are on bad terms with your uncle.
But I won't let anyone be mad
at each other under my command.
Come on.
We have to leave.
The sun of Seljuks...
Mighty Mother Sultan...
spared my life.
She wants loyalty in return.
Loyalty.
However,
she's the one who's not loyal.
What do you have on your mind, my Bey?
Do we have a trick against Ismihan Sultan?
Do I have the power to
make tricks Huseyin?
It's not a trick.
But I will protect myself.
I have to.
I'll do everything Valide Sultan requests...
but as long as I have benefit.
It's enough Huseyin.
It's enough.
One of them wants to tie my
neck with rope...
and one of them wants to
lock me with chains.
I want freedom Huseyin.
In this blessed day...
welcome to our table.
Thank you, my Bey.
In this mubarak Ramadan,
we offer gratitude to our Allah
who gathered us at one table.
- Amin.
- Amin, my Sheikh.
I pray that we can let go of Ramadan in a
way that is pleased with us.
We should always remember
that we are brothers.
Let's try to live together and in peace.
Let's hold onto Allah together.
Amin.
May Ramadan...
- be of help in this purpose, Inshallah.
- Amin.
My dear people, Muslims
are brothers.
The brotherhood of Muslims
is a shield against infidels.
The stronger our brotherhood is...
the more solid our shield will be.
May my Allah make us one of those who
follow His path constantly, Inshallah.
Amin.
Amin, my Sheikh. Amin.
Thanks to my Allah...
thanks to the blessings He
bestowed upon us.
Thanks for our health, and...
thanks for our struggle to keep
following His path.
- Amin.
There is no deity but Allah.
Let's go.
May Allah accept your fasting.
Enjoy your meal.
In the name of Allah, the merciful
and compassionate.
May Allah accept your fasting.
In the name of Allah, the merciful
and compassionate.
Hancı.
Give Nayman food. He'll live
until we arrive in Tabriz.
He will not die until he pays
the price for his betrayal!
Gazan Khan...
will pay the price for
the betrayal, not me.
The dream you believed in
has blinded you.
Why would Gazan Khan pay the price?
You'll be drowned
in Erlik Khan's wrath.
You should be afraid of Allah's wrath.
The bad things you did...
You used the power you
got for evilness.
But we arrived just in time and
protected the seal from you.
Otherwise, what would happen
to these lands?
Osman Bey, me and the
Beys are thankful for your invitation.
We sent the intruder Nayman
from these lands.
I know that Beys are aware of our...
common quest.
Yes, Mother Sultan. Thank you.
Without your help...
there would be no victory.
May you all live long.
But my Bey...
If Mother Sultan wouldn't object at
the beginning, it wouldn't be this hard.
Sometimes differences
might happen, Beys.
We focus on the result.
Victory is our gift from our union.
Celali.
These are my gifts to you.
But of course the biggest gift is...
to reconcile the offended uncle...
with his nephew.
The issues in family are always solved.
There is no issue between
me and my nephew.
Tell me, nephew.
That is true uncle.
Yes, son.
Celali.
Osman Bey, this is a sword used by
Seljuks...
commanders who won a great victory.
Its argil was mixed with
silver and its back is sharp.
That's what good for Osman Bey.
Sharped back. Otherwise, there are a lot of people
who want to attack him from behind.
Osman Bey's justice sword
is enough for him.
There is no need for this,
Mother Sultan.
Osman Bey only needs union.
But if we keep arguing all the time...
it won't be good for anyone.
Turgut Bey is right.
Victories come only with our unity...
and with the permission of my Allah.
Those who want to do
something bad...
will only benefit the enemy.
That's what we are saying my Bey.
We all unite after you.
- There is no need for duality.
- Thank you.
My Bey. We made a decision
with Beys.
Tell me.
As border Beys, we...
won't pay our taxes to the Seljuk...
..but to you.
When infidels come, you fight with them.
When they cause bad things, you solve it.
You even ended the disorder in Konya.
You are stopping the traitors there.
I want to pay my tax to Kayı
tribe, Osman Bey.
We, as Beys and the folks...
want to give our gold to the
one who helps us the most.
Mother Sultan should not be offended.
Time changes.
We should also change.
Beys.
I listened to you
without interrupting you.
I wanted to see the limits
of your rebelliousness.
Pull yourself together...
...or I will make you
pay for it dearly.
No, Mother Sultan.
Stop there.
Perhaps Beys tell the truth.
Let's hear them first.
Sharpen it.
Sharpen it well, Bagatur.
I will kill you with your sword.
You are taking
your power from the seal, Bagatur.
To whom does the seal belong?
The seal belongs to Genghis Khan, Nayman.
Genghis Khan was not a Muslim.
It's a matter of state.
We are protecting the seal from you.
They went to Genghis.
They invited him to Islam.
He always rejected.
You are traitors, the ones
who embraced what Genghis rejected.
Gazan and you..
That seal can only be stained
in the hands of a Muslim.
That seal is only valuable
when in the hands of a man...
...who is blessed by
Sky Tengri (Turkish-Mongolian God)
You dirt Genghis' inheritance, Bagatur.
You betray him.
The seal belongs to the dynasty, Nayman.
It belongs to the state.
You and your brother Talay...
...stole it for your bloody games.
You have no rights on it.
The seal will go to the place
it belongs, to Tabriz, Nayman.
The seal belongs to the ones
who do not betray Genghis.
The seal belongs to me, Bagatur.
You will have been dead
once you understand this.
I will avenge Talay
and take the seal from you.
You will die, Bagatur.
Commander Bagatur.
Nayman is trying to deceive the soldiers.
He wants to cause a disorder
and get away.
Right. I know. Don't worry.
Thank you, thank you.
You honored me, made me proud.
Certainly, the Seljuk State...
...has been going through
difficult times.
But you are right.
While we protect our homeland...
...we should definitely taste...
...power and wealth as well.
But I don't want to ignore...
...Mother Sultan's efforts.
Mother Sultan, you thought
your Bey was a great commander.
You gave him a sword.
And you shared his victory.
So you will give him the half of the taxes.
We shared the hardships.
So there's nothing wrong to
share the power, Osman Bey.
Alright.
Alaaddin Bey.
Write it down.
Osman Bey's law.
The beylics around..
...will pay the half of the tax
they pay to Seljuks...
...to Kayi Tribe...
..from Shawwal Month.
(tenth month of the lunar based Islamic calendar)
Mother Sultan.
We can advance only
by sharing like this. Thank you.
Wolves caught the Seljuk State
among them.
...and they're sharing us.
They're also having iftaar dinner with us.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Thank you, Beys.
Mother Sultan.
Wait a little, wait.
You think you're degraded here.
The sharing wolves die, of course.
But nobody here has such an intention.
Please. Join our alliance.
I said thank you
Osman Bey.
Stay safe.
Stay safe, Mother Sultan.
Stay safe, Beys.
What is this weapon for, brothers?
My Bey must have a plan for it, brother.
It's a little different from the
spearhead we know, huh?
Come on, brothers.
Let's finish this before the sahoor.
We need to produce many more.
Come on.
-Brother.
-Yes?
I've been fasting for days
without eating at sahoor, brother.
-Oh no.
-What can we do about that?
I know.
-I know.
-What?
-Will you find a solution for sahoor?
-I've already found, brother.
You'll see, Gurbuz.
Brothers.
This Cerkutay...
Is he really lunatic?
Brothers, I will play drum
at sahoors from now on.
So there will be no one
who can't wake up for sahoor.
But playing drum is not enough.
We also need to sing.
Wake up at sahoor and do good deeds!
You can't do good by sleeping!
The lazy sleep and do nothing!
Cerkutay won't let you sleep!
-What are you doing here?
-I knew this would work!
-Aykurt.
-Yes brother.
From now on,
alps will play drums at sahoor time.
and everyone will be able to wake up for sahoor!
I'll beat you Cerkutay, come here!
Any news from Karavul, Celali?
He's watching step by step.
They will spend the night in
the caravanserai in Karakuyu.
They will depart in the morning.
What is the shortest way that goes
Tebriz from Karakuyu, Celali?
Kirtca path, Mother Sultan.
Osman!
You will pay for
boasting against Mother Sultan,
and you will see the...
...results of being impertinent.
He thinks he has won now.
He thinks he has the power.
Osman will lose everything he has, Celali.
Such people get rich
when there is no enemy around.
Get the most competent warriors
and best archers ready.
Let Bayindir know.
We will save Nayman,
we will take the seal.
Yes, Mother Sultan.
Alps!
Our new aim...
that we will advance to conquer is Kopruhisar.
We heard that...
Kopruhisar took the greatest precautions.
In fact, they brought huge shields
from Constantinople.
Even if we enter, they will build
a shield wall against us.
If that's the case...
...let's see.
Cerkutay. Baysungur. Bring it.
Alps. Here!
These are the shields
they claim to be impassable.
Cerkutay!
Alps!
Here, look at it carefully, Alps.
The thing that will pass through
these shields...
...is this spear.
Now that these shields
cannot be passed...
...then we will show
you how to pass through them.
Stay strong.
Stand up, come on.
The soldiers with these shields will be...
...on the eastern side of Kopruhisar.
Those who fight there,
the alps who is assigned to fight there...
...will practice this spears.
I don't want a single mistake, alright?
Yes my Bey.
Baysungur. Cerkutay
You heard the commands of attack.
Now let me command for defence.
The Alps who will fight against
the Mongolian cavalry in the forest...
...you will equip this spear as well.
Now we're going to clamp
these spears together.
If strong valiants hold these spears...
...they will never be broken
knocking ten cavalries.
Come on, valiants.
In the name of Allah,
the Compassionate, the Merciful.
Allah is eternal!
Thank you, valiants.
Thank you.
Thanks.
That is all, alps. That is all.
My Bey. Do we need to train against
Mongols since Nayman left?
No.
One leaves..
..but a thousand comes.
These lands will never be left alone
by the enemies.
Right.
The road is safe, Commander Bagatur.
Good. Stay on alert. Send some of the troops
on the right, some on the left.
All of you shall be careful.
No precaution will protect you
from me, Bagatur.
I will kill you with my bare hands!
We have a long way, Nayman.
Do not spend your power by talking.
Come on.
Where is Karavul already, Celali?
Perhaps he got caught, Mother Sultan.
Should I send a scout to the caravansary?
No. Don't you do that.
We will wait.
We will not scare them.
Or else, we cannot take Nayman from them.
He is coming, Mother Sultan.
My Mother Sultan.
The caravan left the caravansary.
They proceed to Tabriz on an
old path to the Kirca route.
Good.
We will first catch them on the way
then we will cut their breaths.
The frontiers did not choose
to be enlightened with my light.
Then Nayman will be freed.
He will bring the darkness for rebels.
Now listen to me carefully about
how we are going to save Nayman.
If Nayman goes then someone
else will come.
Our lands are always in fire circle.
The east is surrounded
the west is hard.
That's why we will always be in training!
-As you say my Bey!
-Good.
Turgut Bey, let's train with you...
-so the alps enjoy it.
-It's an honor Osman Bey.
This is how you
took care of Talay?
I learned how to cheat from the infidels.
But I am not Talay.
Come here.
Well played.
-Well played, my Brave.
-May you live long.
Alps! As you see, you will
always be in training.
But you'll be careful
against the cheaters.
Now everyone,
get back to their training.
The infiltration plan will fail
if Konur does not arrive.
Don't worry. He has never left
any of his duty unfinished.
You go to headquarters.
Check the trainings.
As you say.
When Konur gives the ink and brings the map,
it means the Kopruhisar is ours.
If Allah permits.
-May your path be open.
-Thank you Osman Bey.
Come on Alps!
My loyal soldiers will not leave me alone.
Soldiers! We won't go back without
saving the Almighty Commander Nayman.
Come on!
Traces indicate that
Commander Nayman went this way.
Come on
Be careful.
Help us! Please help us!
My horse is wounded, please!
Let's continue
Commander Bagatur.
Horses are the best friends of Mongols.
We won't turn our backs.
Soldiers. Check it.
Attack!
I bear witness that there is no God but Allah,
and I bear witness that Muhammad is the Messenger...
No.
No. Nayman.
The seal is yours. But you'll give
me what belongs to me first.
What do you want, Ismihan?
Everything in these lands.
May your fight be holy, my Bey.
Thank you, Bala. Thank you.
Osman.
I know this isn't a good time,
but I have something in my mind.
I'll start if you allow.
Tell me, Bala. I'm all ears.
As your reputation spreads,
Turkmens flow to our tribe.
Many have migrated
to Yenisehir recently.
We have many guests and new comers.
I've been thinking...
If we build an almshouse...
...with food available all the time,
...we can help the passengers
and the poor, huh?
Well-thought, Bala.
Really well-thought.
You always back me up. Thank you.
Sure. We should act quickly
for good deeds.
We should be prepared, anyway.
There will be many more comers.
-We should be careful.
-Right, right.
-Thank you, my Bey. May Allah be pleased with you.
-With you too.
Take care of our sons.
Give me your blessings.
You have mine, my Bey. I'll take a good
care of them. May Allah open your way.
Are you lost, foreigner?
This land is dangerous.
You may get in trouble at any time.
So you should give your precious items.
Otherwise, they'll take your life.
I have no precious things. But I'm strong
enough to kill whoever tries to kill me.
Enough!
Innocent people have been
suffering because of bandits like you.
Now it's your turn.
It worths a good deal.
We got what we wanted. Let's go.
Attention!
Come on!
-May your fight be holy, my Bey!
-Thank you.
May Allah help you!
Alcicek.
Aktemur has made peace with his uncle.
I'm so happy about that.
Yes, mother. They are in
good terms, thanks to Allah.
Yes.
But I don't understand.
If Osman Bey was going
to forgive him so easily...
Why did he kick
Aktemur out of the assembly?
No idea.
Maybe, Mother Ayse
talked to Osman Bey.
-Good day, bride!
-Thank you.
What's it?
Where are you going?
Well, Bengi Hatun...
We're going for a good thing.
With Allah's will, we will build an
almshouse in Yenisehir.
So we're going to look for a place for it.
Praise you!
You never stop for a break.
Thank you.
Bride, join us at iftaar today.
Aktemur isn't here, anyway.
So we can have iftaar
woman-to-woman all together, huh?
We will.
Good idea. Thanks.
See you at dinner then.
Good luck.
Listen to me carefully now, Alcicek.
I'll talk to Bala...
...and get involved in this almshouse thing.
-And what will I do, mother?
-You will win people's favor.
As your husband conquered Marmaracik,
you'll conquer people's hearts.
Being a Bey isn't only about conquering.
There are things you should do too.
Alcicek.
Come on. We can't leave such
a big prey to them.
If you want to do big things,
...your move should be big too.
Come on.
Alcicek, be there with such a standing...
...that everyone should think
you're the head of the charity.
Come on.
I saved your life with
only one condition, Nayman.
You'll destroy Osman.
You will step back from
Konya and frontiers.
Everything will be mine.
My life is more precious than
Konya and frontiers.
You will give me the seal.
The seal is useless in your hand.
If I want the seal or your life,
I can take it now, Ismihan.
And these lands will be mine,
why would I accept your offer?
Nayman, I don't feel sorry
for killing anyone.
...to take control of this land.
But if we fight, we will lose our pwoer.
And Osman will be
the one who is going to win.
That's why we will unite
and destroy Osman.
And we both will get what we want.
Osman Bey will learn all of this!
No!
You did what you had to do Ismihan.
And I'll do what you want
by killing Osman.
Who can stand against this army Ismihan?
We'll give what you want.
I am halfway through my life, but I never
betrayed the entrustment. I won't.
Now I'll be your curse.
This was a good raid.
It is very worthy.
This is our territory,
everyone will know this.
Yes.
Ours.
-It's a decent piece.
-Yes.
Now you dropped the brick, bandits.
-May it be easy, Agha.
-Thank you, Malhun Hatun.
Do you have any shortcomings
or complaints?
We don't, thank Allah,
Malhun Hatun.
Tell her the truth!
Why are you keeping silent?
Stay out of this!
Malhun Hatun. Don't listen to them.
They just stay silent and sit still.
What's it?
What wrong?
Merchants from outside
sell everything dearly.
They ask 5 coins
for a one-coin product.
Why are they doing this?
We don't know why. But they are giving
us a hard time. This is out of trade!
Aghas!
Why are we here if you are not going
to tell us your problems?
Don't worry.
We'll solve it for sure.
But do not think of us
as a different person.
If you have a problem,
a complaint, the mansion is there.
Good day.
I'm sorry, Malhun Hatun.
Just as we taught we are back on the
good again with the new leasing law...
...foreign traders began to cripple us.
Mother.
We have to do something about that caravan.
Things are not going well in the marketplace.
Ask all the shopkeepers. Find the merchants
who are doing this to our tradespeople.
Let's understand what their issue is.
They want to defeat us in trades, since they
could not defeat us in the battlefield, mother.
But we will not let them do that.
Come on then, Orhan Bey.
We have a lot of things to do.
So he is getting ready for a siege, huh?
Learn where the quarter is!
If he's at headquarters...
...Yenisehir, which he is proud of,
is defenseless.
Weil get him in such a circle that...
...he won't be able to
get out of there easily.
Neither he nor his family,
not even one of them, will breathe.
Tonight I will wipe Osman
and his family off the earth.
Are you going to kill him at the quarters?
This army will descend on Osman.
What about the mansion?
Why did we stop?
Are you waiting for someone?
Soldiers!
Even if you hadn't come..
...the loyal soldiers would have saved me.
But now, their duty is going to be...
...destroying the mansion of Osman.
This thing will be done tonight.
When everything is over,
I will deal with you, Bayindir.
Sure, sure.
If dogs' prayers were accepted...
Do not wait here! Walk faster!
I'm talking to you
You, huh?
Do not bother yourselves, Beys.
Give that thing in your hand
back to me, you bandit.
That's what you wish for.
Thanks to Allah.
Come on, valiants!
-Are the preparations complete?
-We'll be ready during the night.
We have only one thing missing.
That's the map of passages Konur will bring.
We will receive the map.
And Alps are training.
But we will enter through the passages.
Now tell me.
What will be your move
when the gate is open?
Osman Bey... Now...
Whichever way your gate leads,
we must first open the eastern gate.
This gate is important.
The largest gate is the gate on the east.
We need to attack quickly
and outnumber them at once.
I will make a sudden attack
with the cavalry there.
As for the west and south,
it is close to our archer units.
While the archers will shoot arrows
the infantry will make a sudden attack.
And the infantry will be under
the command of...
..Aktemur.
Konur should have arrived by now.
I hope nothing bad happened to him.
If something bad happens,
Konur will be able to get over it.
Right, brother Boran?
Brothers... Konur has fulfilled duties
even in the Constantine and Konya.
He will fulfill this duty
as well, InshaAllah.
InshaAllah. InshaAllah.
You are right, Boran Alp.
Let's do our duty now.
Horses will not enter
only from the east side.
We can't risk our plan
like that all at once.
Thus, they will enter from the west..
..and the south as well.
As you said, we will start the attack
with horses from another side.
Yes.
The gates must be open for that attack.
And to open the gates, we need...
-The map.
Konur has to come back
as soon as possible.
He will.
He will get over all the hardships...
and he will come.
Don't worry.
Don't forget, Nayman.
You and I both have issues with Osman.
When you destroy
Osman you will give me the lands.
As long as you are loyal to me
you will be in your lands
however you want.
Ismihan, I need loyal people not rebels.
Karancu.
You'll be the head of soldiers.
After the sunset, you'll raid the mansion.
Not even a single person
will survive there.
You will not capture old people...
...children or women. Come on.
Kam.
Bayindir.
You wanted to be forgiven.
Now this is your chance.
You'll go to Yenisehir with Karancu
and the (Mongol) soldiers.
Every drop of blood you shed from
Osman's house
will take you one step further
towards forgiveness, Bayindir.
I'll do everything to be forgiven by you,
Hadhrat Mother Sultan.
Come on.
Prepare a unity
with the strongest and
the most talented soldiers.
I will.
I will. But it feels wrong, my Bey.
This oppression is too much.
We will pay for this in the after life.
Yes Huseyin. We will.
You do as I say. Come on.
Alright.
Yenisehir
Osman Bey's Mansion
Did you find the location of the Hospice, Bala?
We searched but we couldn't find a place for it.
It has to be somewhere in the center.
We'll check again tomorrow.
We also want to do our best Bala Hatun.
Do not think of us separately.
May you live long Bengi Hatun.
Alcicek is also very ambitious.
We'll do this together.
-She told me.
Don't worry about the
construction business, Bala Hatun.
There is a good bricklayer we know.
I already informed him.
MashaAllah Bengi Hatun.
You rushed.
We just talked about it today.
Good deeds must be
done quickly, Ayse Hatun.
Well done, Bengi Hatun.
You compete a lot in charity.
Alcicek, I know you just married.
But when do you want to have children?
Mother! Why are you talking
about this in here?!
mother, other one is her mother in law,
and the others are her aunts in law.
And don't you know why I am asking?
-Yes.
Besides, my mother is a midwife.
They've got married recently, The Dark Midwife.
There will be a time for that too.
There isn't a proper time for a baby, Bengi Hatun.
If a baby arrived...
...our house would be full of joy with
a baby's sound. Right, The Dark Midwife?
Yes. Yes.
-Can I come in?
-Come in, Esma.
Bala Hatun, Halime...
I just couldn't put her to sleep.
She must have heard her aunt Ayse.
Let me check her.
Eat some dessert, daughter.
Let's say we captured Kopruhisar.
What is the next?
Once we capture Kopruhisar,
we'll move according to the information.
But I want to take the lands
up to Koyunhisar quickly.
-Right.
-My Bey.
Shall we send a few alps after Konur?
It's being late.
If they know about us,
they will close the passes.
He'll arrive sooner or later.
But tell me...
Are alps watching around the headquarters?
Alps never sleep.
-They watch all around.
-Alright.
Until we get news from Konur...
..let's see whether alps are ready or not.
Something must have happened to him.
Otherwise, he would be here now.
Brother, I assume...
My Bey is coming. Come on.
Alps, we will march towards
Kopruhisar after the morning prayer.
My Bey, is there some news from Konur?
No.
Not yet.
In any case,
we will march to Kopruhisar.
Intelligence is the key of victory.
Without it...
we will take the rough path. But with
Allah's permission, we will receive news.
Thank you my Bey.
If Allah permits, if Allah permits.
The arrow will hit the target Osman Bey.
No difficulty will be able to stop us.
Thank you, thank you.
- Boran!
- My Bey?
Play the qopuz.
Play it and let us enjoy.
Yes my Bey.
I am burning with the love of Muhammed PBUH
I am deeply following Muhammad (PBUH)
I am burning with the love of Muhammad (PBUH)
I am deeply following the path of Muhammad (PBUH)
His Ummah(community)
is always grateful
My Allah, make me fall
in love with Muhammed!
I pray endlessly to Allah, the Almighty
So that there shall be no love in my
heart apart from Muhammad's (PBUH)
I am burning with the love of Muhammad (PBUH)
I am deeply following the path of Muhammad (PBUH)
Burn the mansion from inside.
When Yenisehir sees the flares,
they will all have died.
No daughter, no Halime.
What's wrong with you my child?
May my beautiful daughter go to sleep.
My Halime.
Bengi Hatun, eat halva.
Any news from the alps
we sent after Nayman?
No news yet. But I can see that
there is something that bothers you.
What happened Osman Bey?
We go to the west, you think about the east,
we go to the east, you don't forget the west.
-There is something that bothers you.
-He always suffered, never found comfort
You are the miracle of Muhammad's (PBUH) grief
I am burning with the love of Muhammad (PBUH)
I am deeply following the path of Muhammad (PBUH)
The Shah of Shahs asked for
the forgiveness of his ummah
We do not have to fear the Day of Resurrection,
thanks to Muhammad (PBUH)
I'd be dispersed by your grace, my Allah
Give me a drop
from the sea of Muhammad (PBUH)
As I am burning with the love of Muhammad (PBUH)
I am deeply following the path of Muhammad (PBUH)
I choose to be taken over...
...By love for Muhammad (PBUH)
Poor Yesevi longs to see the blessed grave
Will I be granted to reach your feet's soil
As I am burning with the love of Muhammad (PBUH)
I am deeply following the path of Muhammad (PBUH)
Praise be.
Thank you Boran. Thank you.
Thank you, my Bey.
-They're attacking
-Alps!
Alps!
My Halime.
Alps! They're attacking
-Osman!
-Nayman.
I promised you,
I said I would come to kill you.
I have the seal,
I have the power. All you have left is death!
Fire!
Not only yourself, your loved ones
will also die tonight Osman!
Yenisehir is burning,
you headquarters is burning
Your fire will be your hell.
Turgut. Take alps and go east.
Don't let them surround us!
Come with me to the east alps! Come on!
-Boran. Go after them.
-Gather your arrows brave boys
-Come on!
-Show them your arrows!
-Cerkutay. Go to south.
-Come on brothers!
Aktemur, come with me. Come on.
-Come on!
- Hide, Alaeddin.
Malhun! Bala!
-Mother!
-Mother Malhun!
-Orhan!
-Mother, are you all right?
-Alaeddin!
-Are you all right mother?
O Haqq!
O Allah!
Visit our website for more: turkision.com